<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Crashlanded.label>Marooned</Crashlanded.label>
  <Crashlanded.description>The three of you awake in your bunks to the sounds of howling wind, cracking thunder, and splitting wood. You barely get to the life boats before the ship is torn apart by the terrible storm. Some time later, you land on this unknown landmass.</Crashlanded.description>
  <Crashlanded.scenario.name>Marooned</Crashlanded.scenario.name>
  <Crashlanded.scenario.summary>Three marooned survivors - the classic RimWorld experience.</Crashlanded.scenario.summary>
  <Crashlanded.scenario.description>The three of you awake in your bunks to the sounds of howling wind, cracking thunder, and splitting wood. You barely get to the life boats before the ship is torn apart by the terrible storm. Some time later, you land on this unknown landmass.</Crashlanded.scenario.description>
  <Crashlanded.scenario.parts.14.text>The three of you awake in your bunks to the sounds of howling wind, cracking thunder, and splitting wood. You barely get to the life boats before the ship is torn apart. Some time later, you land on this unknown landmass.</Crashlanded.scenario.parts.14.text>
  <TheRichExplorer.label>The Rich Explorer</TheRichExplorer.label>
  <TheRichExplorer.description>People called you crazy for leaving your home, but you always yearned to explore the world - outside the adventure novels. Now you're at the end of your long journey, landing on an unknown landmass to see what it's like.\n\nNote: Since your starting character will lack some skills, this is an especially difficult scenario in the early game.</TheRichExplorer.description>
  <TheRichExplorer.scenario.name>The Rich Explorer</TheRichExplorer.scenario.name>
  <TheRichExplorer.scenario.summary>One rich explorer out to experience the world. Extra difficult.</TheRichExplorer.scenario.summary>
  <TheRichExplorer.scenario.description>People called you crazy for leaving your home, but you always yearned to explore the world - outside the adventure novels. Now you're at the end of your long journey, landing on an unknown landmass to see what it's like.\n\nNote: Since your starting character will lack some skills, this is an especially difficult scenario in the early game.</TheRichExplorer.scenario.description>
  <TheRichExplorer.scenario.parts.11.text>The riches, glamor, and free-orgies were never enough for you. You wanted more - the grit and consequence of real life, like they talk about in the history books. You wanted to know what real challenge and consequence feel like.\n\nNow, after a journey years in the making, you're landing on this unknown landmass. Real consequences await you.</TheRichExplorer.scenario.parts.11.text>
</LanguageData>
